<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><news>
<item>
	<id>51</id>
	<title>Capital One Cup Standings</title>
	<date>06/01/2012</date>
	<description>See how your school stacks up. Standings are updated after each NCAA Championship has concluded and official results are posted.</description>
	<url>http://www.capitalonecup.com/standings</url>
</item>
<item>
	<id>48</id>
	<title>2012 Men’s Final Four and Beyond</title>
	<date>03/30/2012</date>
	<description>Heading into the Men’s Final Four in New Orleans we had the chance to catch up with Clark Kellogg, Capital One Cup Advisory Board member and CBS lead college basketball analyst, in his hometown of Columbus, Ohio.  We asked him a few questions about the mystique of the Final Four in New Orleans, the challenge of playing in a dome and his thoughts on teams to watch out for next season.


Q: New Orleans has been known for some special Final Four memories over the years.  Why does it seem that crazy things happen in the Big Easy, such as Fred Brown’s pass, Chris Webber’s time out and Keith Smart’s game winning shot?
A:  I have absolutely no idea but it is unbelievable. Take a look at this year’s Final Four – it’s pretty amazing to have two teams from the same state in Kentucky and Louisville.  I am interested to see what the state of Kentucky brings to this year’s tournament.  It will be a battle between instate rivals to see who can earn the most points for the Capital One Cup during this tournament.  The winner on Monday earns 60 crucial points toward their total and will move up in the Cup rankings. My colleague, Jim Nantz, has been at numerous Final Fours in New Orleans and the last time that I was here was in 2003, so it’s been awhile.  For sure it will be interesting and I’m excited to see what will transpire.


Q: The Final Four has been played in a center court dome configuration the last few years.  What kind of challenge does this present to players who have never experienced this in terms of depth perception when shooting and just getting comfortable in such an expansive setting?
A: It is very difficult for players who haven’t played in this type of environment before.  It will take them some time to adjust to the size of the arena.  Basketball is designed to be played in an intimate setting.  Someday I would love for the tournament to go back to a smaller arena.  


Q: Among the players in the Final Four, who should fans keep their eye on in the future once their college careers are done?
A:  I think that Kentucky’s Anthony Davis, Kansas’ Thomas Robinson, Kentucky’s Terrence Jones, Ohio State’s Jared Sullinger and Kentucky’s Darius Miller will all have great careers in the NBA when the time comes.  Fans should continue to watch these guys once they leave the collegiate world and head out to the next level.


Q: Which teams should we watch out for in 2012-13?
A:  I have my eye on a few teams for next season.  I think that Creighton and Iowa will have tremendous seasons next year.  I also think that North Carolina State and Louisville will return strong next year.  They have a lot of young players on their team and will be sure to improve next year.


Q: After the championship game is played on Monday night and this year’s version of March Madness is in the books what do you and your family have planned?
A: I am going to take a break for a few days and then it is back to the grind.  I plan to return to my duties as vice president of the Indiana Pacers.  I’m really looking forward to spending Easter at home with my family.</description>
	<url>http://www.capitalonecup.com/news?id=5e19f548-0301-4987-92cc-d59357147e55</url>
</item>
<item>
	<id>47</id>
	<title>Inaugural Year of Capital One Cup Culminates at Star-Studded ESPY Awards</title>
	<date>07/25/2011</date>
	<description>The star-studded ESPY Awards got off to a dazzling start Wednesday night with the Red Carpet walk into the Nokia Theater. 

Featured among the many current athletes and entertainers were the Capital One Cup Advisory Board members, who proceeded down the famed path in front of cheering fans and flashing cameras as they represented the Capital One Cup. Rece Davis, Doug Flutie, Clark Kellogg, Lisa Leslie and Robin Ventura all made the walk and were all on hand to watch as the inaugural Capital One Cup was awarded at the 19th Annual ESPY Awards.

This year's event was special because it marked the culmination of the first year of the Capital One Cup and the chance for Capital One to formally present the men's and women's trophies for overall NCAA Division I athletics excellence to the winning schools in front of millions of television viewers.

On hand to receive the trophies from pop music icon Justin Timberlake on behalf of their schools were Chiney Okwumike and Nneka Ogwumike, women’s basketball players for Stanford University, winner of the women's Capital One Cup, as well as Chandler Parsons, men’s basketball player for the University of Florida, winner of the men's Capital One Cup. In addition to the trophy, the schools will also receive a $200,000 scholarship for post-graduate studies for their student athletes.</description>
	<url>http://www.capitalonecup.com/news?id=cf527e98-0c79-4113-a359-a53c1ecea109</url>
</item>
<item>
	<id>46</id>
	<title>Standings</title>
	<date>04/23/2012</date>
	<description>See how your school stacks up. Standings are updated after each NCAA Championship has concluded and official results are posted.</description>
	<url>http://www.capitalonecup.com/standings</url>
</item>
</news>
