<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><merch>
<item>
	<id>142</id>
	<title>PLAY-A-THON Fundraising Kit</title>
	<imageurl>http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/Files_Main/200/EPK032d0d73c_Main400.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Now you can plan your own fundraising event and support your favorite cause simply by playing and having fun! Organize a PLAY-A-THON and let everyone play their favorite games and activities while making a difference in support of your school, church or favorite charity.]]></description>
	<price>$79.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/play-a-thon-fundraising-kit-for-ages-9-12?BR=485&ID=20422]]></buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>141</id>
	<title>BATTLESHIP Live Game</title>
	<imageurl>http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/Files_Main/200/82F41A375056900B107D26F5E0C60FE9.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Go live! In this fun version of the classic BATTLESHIP game, the electronic talking tower calls the plays! With motion sensing, sound effects and even surprise game-changing events, the tower guides the game from start to finish while you plot your strategy and command your ships. Launch the spy plane to spot your enemy and use your ship's special powers to sweep for minds, launch air attacks, fire missiles and more. With so many things to do, this "naval battle" is more thrilling than ever! Includes electronic tower, gameboard, 2 divider screens, 10 ships, 2 cannons, 2 command pegs, spy plane and track and startup guide. Requires 4 "AA" batteries (not included). Adult assembly required. For 2 players. Ages 8 and up.
]]></description>
	<price>$45.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/battleship-live-game?BR=673&ID=28836]]></buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>140</id>
	<title>BATTLESHIP FUN ON THE RUN Game </title>
	<imageurl>http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/Files_Main/200/2A60C0B35056900B10AF848E6FA0185A.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Play a round of your BATTLESHIP game anytime, anywhere with this awesome set! The convenient, self-contained storage cases doubles as the interlocking game units, so you can open them up and start playing wherever you are. Set up your ship pieces on your side of the board and then try to narrow down where your opponent has put his. Make enough "strikes" on his ships and you'll sink them all to win!


Includes 10 ships, 2 game units, red pegs, white pegs and instructions.
For 2 players.


Ages 7 and up.]]></description>
	<price>$5.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/battleship-fun-on-the-run-game?BR=673&ID=28257]]></buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>139</id>
	<title>Battleship (game)</title>
	<imageurl>http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/Files_Main/200/9DB488515056900B10A8F458C626B7BA.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Dare to defeat the enemy fleet in this classic game of strategic combat. Command a fleet of five ships as you search out the enemy, fire at coordinates and score hits. Can you sink your opponent's fleet before your opponent sinks yours?

Swift and strategic missile assaults will take down your opponent - but only if you've hidden your ships from counter attacks! Track each and every hit and miss, keep your cool under fire, and you just might keep your game afloat.

You can take your BATTLESHIP game anywhere with the portable fold-up trays!

Comes with 2 plastic fold-and-store game trays, 10 plastic ships, 84 red "hit" pegs, 168 white "miss" pegs, label sheet and instructions.

For two players.

Ages 7 and up.]]></description>
	<price>$17.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.hasbrotoyshop.com/battleship-game-36934?BR=673&ID=28841]]></buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
</merch>
