<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><merch>
<item>
	<id>134</id>
	<title>San Francisco 49ers Super Bowl XVI Collectors Pin</title>
	<imageurl>http://images.footballfanatics.com/FFImage/thumb.aspx?i=%2fproductImages%2f_664000%2fff_664195_xl.jpg&w=400</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Proudly commemorate the San Francisco 49ers' 26-21 victory over the Cincinnati Bengals in Super Bowl XVI with this Champions collectors pin! Featuring vibrant team graphics and bold champs lettering celebrating the 1982 game held in Pontiac, Michigan, this pin is perfect for showing off your team's big win!]]></description>
	<price>$20.00</price>
	<buyinfo>http://www.shop49ers.com/San_Francisco_49ers_Hats/San_Francisco_49ers_Super_Bowl_XVI_Collectors_Pin</buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>133</id>
	<title>Reebok San Francisco 49ers Scarlet-Black 2011 Sideline Players Adjustable Visor </title>
	<imageurl>http://images.footballfanatics.com/FFImage/thumb.aspx?i=%2fproductImages%2f_672000%2fff_672833_xl.jpg&w=400</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[An NFL player dons his pads and jersey before emerging onto the field to do battle with the opposing team. It is a fan’s duty to also properly outfit oneself, to make sure their team is well-represented as they engage in combat to determine gridiron supremacy. Cap off your team-spirited attire by making sure your San Francisco pride is displayed in official team style with this Reebok Sideline Players visor! Worn by your favorite players on the sideline, this visor features an embroidered team logo on the front and a woven team name on the back. It’s an ideal show of team pride and your solidarity with your 49ers!
]]></description>
	<price>$19.95</price>
	<buyinfo>http://www.shop49ers.com/San_Francisco_49ers_Hats/Reebok_San_Francisco_49ers_Scarlet-Black_2011_Sideline_Players_Adjustable_Visor</buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>132</id>
	<title>Reebok San Francisco 49ers 2011 Scarlet Coaches On-Field Adjustable Hat</title>
	<imageurl>http://images.footballfanatics.com/FFImage/thumb.aspx?i=%2fproductImages%2f_663000%2fff_663232_xl.jpg&w=400</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Make the right call for your 49ers pride by sporting the same style cap worn by your favorite team’s coaching staff! The Reebok On-Field Coaches hat features an embroidered team logo on the crown, a woven team name on the back strap and team-colored accents on the bill. Your San Francisco enthusiasm will be large, in charge and ready to take on the competition!
]]></description>
	<price>$19.95</price>
	<buyinfo>http://www.shop49ers.com/San_Francisco_49ers_Hats/Reebok_San_Francisco_49ers_2011_Scarlet_Coaches_On-Field_Adjustable_Hat</buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>131</id>
	<title>San Francisco 49ers Ash Critical Victory V Sweatpants</title>
	<imageurl>http://images.footballfanatics.com/FFImage/thumb.aspx?i=%2fproductImages%2f_677000%2fff_677493_xl.jpg&w=400</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Be ready for crunch time even when you're laying around the house with these Critical Victory V sweatpants! They feature a bold team logo, "49ers Football" lettering and Conference logo down the left leg, and are complemented by non-elastic bottom cuffs for a loose and comfy fit around your ankles!]]></description>
	<price>$34.95</price>
	<buyinfo>http://www.shop49ers.com/San_Francisco_49ers_Mens_Shorts_And_Pants/San_Francisco_49ers_Ash_Critical_Victory_V_Sweatpants</buyinfo>
	<asin></asin>
	<buylink></buylink>
</item>
</merch>
