<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><merch>
<item>
	<id>189</id>
	<title>Gamma Green Hulk Smash Fists</title>
	<imageurl>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71rSl0-BAOL._SL1500_.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[Become incredible, just like the hulk, with these Gamma Green Hulk Smash Fists! These green foam fists have an elastic inside that you can hold so you have a better grasp. When the Hulk leaps into battle there's nothing that can stop him from smashing everything in his path. Pick up these Hasbro foam fists for your Hulk youngster.]]></description>
	<price>$19.96</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Gamma-Green-Hulk-Smash-Fists/dp/B008H7MH86%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAJOVXUYQSRTJH2K6Q%26tag%3Drepubproje-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3DB008H7MH86]]></buyinfo>
	<asin>B008H7MH86  </asin>
	<buylink><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/gp/dmusic/order/one-click-interstitial.html?ie=UTF8&ASIN=B008H7MH86  &isTrack=1&tryInPlace=0]]></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>188</id>
	<title>Diamond Select Toys Marvel Select: Avengers Movie Hawkeye Action Figure</title>
	<imageurl>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41hg9OegQpL._SL160_.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[A Diamond Select Release! Designed and Sculpted by Gentle Giant! The Avengers movie is almost upon us, and Diamond Select building up the team! First up is the newest recruit, and the worlds greatest marksman, Hawkeye! Based on the likeness of actor Jeremy Renner, this 7inchscale Marvel Select figure comes with his trademark bow and arrows, and will look perfect alongside your other Select Avengers. Plus, it features 16 points of articulation, for a variety of action poses! Hawkeye comes with a detailed display base in oversized collector packaging, and is only available on the specialty market!]]></description>
	<price>$21.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Diamond-Select-Toys-Marvel-Avengers/dp/B006WYL002%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAJOVXUYQSRTJH2K6Q%26tag%3Drepubproje-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3DB006WYL002]]></buyinfo>
	<asin>B006WYL002  </asin>
	<buylink><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/gp/dmusic/order/one-click-interstitial.html?ie=UTF8&ASIN=B006WYL002  &isTrack=1&tryInPlace=0]]></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>187</id>
	<title>Avengers Power Attack Iron Man 10</title>
	<imageurl>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/4157rjrwjKL._SL160_.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[The mighty IRON MAN Mark VII is the single most powerful piece of combat hardware ever constructed. The armor is tough enough to withstand a nuclear blast, and the weaponry is equal to the most advanced battleships available. Unstoppable and invincible, this is the armor that makes IRON MAN one of the heavy hitters on the AVENGERS.This detailed IRON MAN Mark VII puts you right into the heart of the battle for the future of the planet. Hear your hero intimidate the enemy with battle cries and combat sounds. He wont back down in the starkest of circumstances. Lift his arm to deploy missile blasters, and let the enemy know he will not accept defeat.Figure comes with 2 launching missiles.]]></description>
	<price>$24.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Avengers-Power-Attack-Iron-Figure/dp/B006CBZYCA%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAJOVXUYQSRTJH2K6Q%26tag%3Drepubproje-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3DB006CBZYCA]]></buyinfo>
	<asin>B006CBZYCA  </asin>
	<buylink><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/gp/dmusic/order/one-click-interstitial.html?ie=UTF8&ASIN=B006CBZYCA  &isTrack=1&tryInPlace=0]]></buylink>
</item>
<item>
	<id>186</id>
	<title>Avengers Mighty Strike Thor 10</title>
	<imageurl>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41xI2pxzi-L._SL160_.jpg</imageurl>
	<description><![CDATA[The mighty THOR has come to Earth to face down any evil that threatens humanity. Every blow of his mighty hammer shatters the air like thunder. When he calls down the fury of the storms that are his to command, no enemy can stand against him. With the other AVENGERS by his side, he is absolutely unbeatable.This detailed THOR figure puts you right into the heart of the battle for the future of the planet. Hear your hero intimidate the enemy with battle cries and combat sounds. He wont back down in the starkest of circumstances. Lift his arm to send his hammer flying, and let the enemy know he will not accept defeat.Figure comes with launching hammer.]]></description>
	<price>$24.99</price>
	<buyinfo><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/Avengers-Mighty-Strike-Thor-Figure/dp/B006CC023K%3FSubscriptionId%3DAKIAJOVXUYQSRTJH2K6Q%26tag%3Drepubproje-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3DB006CC023K]]></buyinfo>
	<asin>B006CC023K  </asin>
	<buylink><![CDATA[http://www.amazon.com/gp/dmusic/order/one-click-interstitial.html?ie=UTF8&ASIN=B006CC023K  &isTrack=1&tryInPlace=0]]></buylink>
</item>
</merch>
